而且 你们有过特氟龙导致的不孕事件
Moreover, you have infertility at Teflon.
白血病事件
Occurrences of leukemia.
癌症高发
You have excess of cancers.
包括膀胱癌 肾癌 口腔癌 咽喉癌
Bladder, kidney, oral, pharynx.
下一段 78号证据
Next paragraph. 78.
您看到这个标题了吗 您看到这个日期了吗 您看到了吗
Do you see that heading? Do you see that date? Do you see that?
96号证据 53号证据
Exhibit 96. Exhibit 53.
我想谈谈先天缺陷的部分
I'd like to move on to birth defects.
这个已经进行了快七个小时了
We've gone almost seven hours.
霍利迪先生 您知不知道在1981年
Mr. Holliday, you're aware that in 1981
3M告知杜邦他们在老鼠身上进行了研究
3M notified DuPont that it had conducted studies on rats.
这些研究表明
And these studies showed
持续暴露在C-8中会导致面部畸形
that sustained C-8 exposure can cause facial deformities?